BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Bowaters Southern Paper Corporation, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Container Corporation of America, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Code no.3351: Vickers Incorporated Division, Sperry Rand Corporation, Omaha Plant and International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 171, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3646: Noma Lites, Inc. and Electrical Workers Local Union 545, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Code no.1446: Milwaukee Lithographers and Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, Local 7-L, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Code no.1600: Nitrogen Division, Allied Chemical Corporation and United Mine Workers of America, District 50, Local 12103, 1961- 1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Code no.1601: Solvay Process Division, Allied Chemical Corporation and United Mine Workers of America, District 50, Local 12457, 1960- 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Code no.1604: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and Chemical Workers Association, Inc., 1959-1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Code no.1606: Ethyl Corporation and International Union of District 40, United Mine Workers of America, 1956-1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    1956-1958, 1967-1971
  - Code no.1610: Hooker Chemical Corporation and Niagara Hooker Employees Union, 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Code no.1611: Monsanto and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 12, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Code no.1613: National Lead Co., Titanium Division and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, Local 13-366, 1959-1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Code no.1615: Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation and United Mine Workers of America, District 50, Local 14901, 1960-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Code no.1618: Union Carbide Corporation, Oak Ridge Plant and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 3-288, 1964-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Code no.1619: Union Carbide Corporation, Nuclear Division and Atomic Trades and Labor Council, AFL-CIO, Local 480, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Code no.1625: American Viscose Corporation, Film Division and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, CLC, Local 713, 1959- 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Code no.1626: Beaunit Fibers and United Textile Workers Union of America, Local 2207, 1962-1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Code no.1627: Celanese Fibers Company and United Mine Workers of America, Local 15153, 1960-1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Code no.1628: Celanese Corporation of America and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, Local 1093, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Code no.1629: Celanese Fibers Company and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, Local 1874, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Code no.1630: Dow Chemical Company, Midland, Michigan and United Mine Workers of America, Local 12075, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Code no.1632: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and Martinsville Nylon Employees' Council Corporation, 1961-1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Code no.1634: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and United Workers, Inc., Waynesboro, Virginia, 1961-1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Code no.1636: Hercules Powder Company and International Chemical Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 271, 1958-1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Code no.1639: Rohm and Haas Company and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 88, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Code no.1640: Spaulding Fibre Company and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2106, AFL-CIO, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Code no.3307: Linde Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-215, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Code no.2350: American Can Company, Glass Operations and Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Locals 132,129,119, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2369: Shenango Ceramics, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Production and Maintenance Employees, 1965-1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Code no.1002: Hammond-California Redwood Co. and Lumber and Sawmill Workers' Union, Local 2592,3006, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Code no.1003: Potlatch Forests, Inc. and International Woodworkers of America, Local 5-484, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1004: Potlatch Forests, Inc. and International Woodworkers of America, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Code no.1006: Weyerhaeuser Company and International Woodworkers of America, Local 3-536,3-11, 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Code no.1007: Douglas Fir Plywood Mills and Plywood and Veneer Workers Union, District 9, 1950-1955 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Code no.1009: Southern California Lumber Employers, Los Angeles, CA and Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union, Local 2288, 1966- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Code no.1011: Woodworkers Association of Chicago and Chicago District Council of Carpenters, AFL-CIO, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Code no.1015: Edward Hines Lumber Co. and Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union, Local 2288, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Code no.1020: Prestige Structures, Inc. and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, Local 335, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Code no.1023: Edward Hines Lumber Co. and Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union, Locals 2902,2589, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Code no.1024: Georgia-Pacific Corporation and Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union, Locals 2592,3006, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Code no.1025: Home Builders Association and Central Wisconsin District of Carpenters, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Code no.1026: Masonite Corporation and International Woodworkers of America, 1964-1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Code no.1101: Magnavox Company of Tennessee and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 748, 1969- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Code no.1200: Consolidated Papers, Inc. Consoweld Corporation and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Locals 187,115,359, 1963- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Series V: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.2309: Corning Glass Works, Albion Plant and American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 1006, 1960- 1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Code no.2320: Glass, Glazing and Mirror Contractors of Los Angeles and Vicinity and Glaziers, Glass Workers and Glass Warehouse Workers Local 636, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Code no.2609: Revere Copper and Brass Incorporated, Rome Division and Mechanics Education Society of America, AFL-CIO, Local 56, 1962- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2610: Reynolds Metal Company and International Union, United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2611: Reynolds Metals Company, Alloys Plant and Aluminum Workers' International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 200, 1965-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2615: Aluminum Company of America and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1050, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2616: Erie Forge and Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 1573, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2617: Ladish Company and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1958- 1961 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2619: McLouth Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 1573, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2620: Zanesville Armco Independent Organization, Inc. and Armco Steel Corporation, Zanesville Works, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2625: Washington Metal Trades, Inc. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 158, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2629: Aluminum Company of America and Aluminum Trades Council of Vancouver, Washington, 1965-1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2634: Harvey's Aluminum, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 6700, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2635: Union Carbide Corporation, Stellite Division, Kokomo, Indiana and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2958, 1965- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2642: Oregon District Foundry Operators and International Molders and Allied Workers' Union of North America, Local 139, 1967- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2645: Reynolds Metals Company, Alloys Plant and Reduction Plant and Muscle Shoals Building and Construction Trades Council, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Code no.2646: G.H.R. Foundry Division of the Dayton Malleable Iron Company and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 756, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Code no.2652: Woodward Iron Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2969, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Code no.2661: Western Electric Company, Inc., Buffalo Plant and Communications Workers of America, Local 1162, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Code no.2664: Manufacturers' Industrial Relations Association and International Molders and Allied Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 158, 1970- 1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Code no.2900: American Can Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Code no.2901: American Can Company and Federal Labor Union, Local 23393, AFL-CIO, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Code no.2902: American Can Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1959-1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Code no.2903: Continental Can Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Code no.2904: Continental Can Company, Inc. and International Association of Machinists, 1960-1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Code no.2905: National Can Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Code no.2907: National Lock Company, Rockford, Illinois and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 449, 1958-1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Code no.2911: Walker Manufacturing Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 85 and 660, 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Code no.2913: American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation, Baltimore Plant and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 344, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Code no.2914: Coleman Company of Wichita, Kansas and International Union of District 50 Allied and Technical Workers, Local 15393, 1959- 1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Code no.2917: National-U.S. Radiator Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Code no.2918: Scovil Manufacturing Company, Waterbury Divisions and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 1604, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Code no.2920: Trane Company and La Crosse Trane Lodge, No. 21, International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, 1959-1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Code no.2922: American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation, Youngstown Kitchens Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Code no.3352: R. Hoe and Co. Printing Press Manufacturing Division and District Lodge 15, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3358: Dodge Manufacturing Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1191, AFL-CIO, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3360: Reed Drilling Tools Division; G.W. Murphy Industries, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2083, 1968- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3369: Vickers Division of Sperry Rand Corporation, Joplin Plant and Allied Industrial Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1968- 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Code no.3374: Lufkin Industries, Inc. and AFL-CIO, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3379: Contract Shops and Metal Trades Council of Portland and Vicinity, AFL-CIO, 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3381: New Britain Machine Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Lodge 1021, 1967- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3383: Hesston Manufacturing Company, Inc. and Hesston Manufacturing Worker's Association, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3387: Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company, York Plant and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1400, 1966- 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3388: ACF Industries and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1303 of District 37, 1966- 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3390: Fedders Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 485, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3392: Norge, Fedders Corp., Effingham Plant and Stove, Furnace, and Allied Appliance Workers International Union, Local 105, AFL-CIO, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3601: Federal Pacific Electric Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1159, 1966- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Code no.3602: I-T-E Circuit Breaker Company and Electrical Switchgear Union, 1967-1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Code no.3603: ITT Kellogg and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 713, 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Code no.3604: Pennsylvania Transformer Division and United Steelworkers of America, Local 3968, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Code no.3607: Geo. D. Roper Corporation and Metal Trades Department, AFL-CIO, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Code no.3611: Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company, Norwood, Ohio and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 765, 1958-1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Code no.3612: Century Electric Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Code no.3613: Alliance Manufacturing Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 750, 1959- 1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Code no.3619: Reliance Electric and Engineering Company, Master Electric Division and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, Local 2154, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Code no.3620: Reliance Electric Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 737, 1968- 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Code no.3621: Robbins and Myers, Inc. and United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 902, 1959- 1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Code no.3623: O.A. Sutton Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Lodge No. 70, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Code no.3625: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Code no.3630: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Association of Machinists, District Lodge 93, 1952-1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Code no.3631: Kelvinator, Division of American Motors Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 206, 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Code no.2633: Fedders Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Local 554, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Code no.3636: Landers, Frary and Clark and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 207, 1959-1965 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Code no.3637: Maytag Company and International Union, United Automobile Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 997, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Code no.3638: Diehl Manufacturing Co. and Diehl Employees' Independent Union, Inc., 1956-1963 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Code no.3639: Singer Company Metrics Division, Bridgeport Plant and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 227, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Code no.3644: Chicago Lighting Equipment Manufacturers' Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 134, 1961-1970 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Code no.3647: New York Lamp and Shade Manufacturers' Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3, 1967- 1972 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Code no.3648: Ohio Brass Company and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, Locals 2157 and 2158, 1959-1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Code no.3281: Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1968- 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3282: Thomas A. Edison Industries; McGraw-Edison Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 467, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3284: National Cash Register Company and NCR Employees' Independent Union, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3285: Royal McBee Corporation and Royal Industrial Union, Local 937, AFL-CIO, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3286: Univac, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 334, 1961- 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Code no.3287: Univac, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2047, 1967- 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3288: Sperry Rand Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Local Lodge 826, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3289: Underwood Corporation, Bridgewood Works and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 267, 1956-1959 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3290: Underwood Corporation, Hartford Works and International Association of Machinists, Lodges 19,350,354,35, AFL-CIO, 1962- 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3291: Midwest Manufacturing Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2063, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3292: Borg-Warner Corporation, York Division and Ice Machinery Independent Employees' Association, 1961-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3293: Chrysler Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 775, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3294: Copeland Refrigeration Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 725, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3297: Hussmann Refrigerator Co. and American Federation of Labor and Affiliated AFL-CIO Organizations, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Code no.3298: Philco-Ford Corporation, Appliance Division and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, CLC, Local 919, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Code no.3299: Tecumseh Products Company and United Product Workers of Tecumseh, Michigan, 1959-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Code no.3302: Koppers Company, Inc., Metal Products Division and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Memorial Lodge 1784, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Code no.3303: New York Air Brake Company, Watertown Division and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 761, District 137, 1959- 1962 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Code no.3305: Washington Metal Trades, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 79, 1965- 1971 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Code no.3308: Monroe Calculating Machine Company, Bristol Division and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, Lodge 770, 1961- 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Code no.3309: Alco Products, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2286, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Code no.3310: United Engineering and Foundry Company, Youngstown Plant and U.E. & F Employees' Association, 1960- 1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Code no.3313: Avco New Idea Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Code no.3315: Ingersoll-Rand Company and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1962-1971 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Code no.3318: Waukesha Motor Company and International Association of Machinists, Local 1377, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Code no.3321: Morse Chain Company and Ithaca Machinists Lodge 1607, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Code no.3323: United Engineering and Foundry Company, Vandergrift Plant and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1968 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Code no.3324: Burroughs Corporation and United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1313, 1971- 1974 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Code no.3326: Cessna Aircraft Company and International Association of Machinists, 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Code no.3327: Fruehauf Corporation, Strick Trailers Division and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 585, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Code no.3328: Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company, Independence Plant and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1958, 1964- 1971 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Code no.3330: Leesona Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1605, District 64, 1965- 1973 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Code no.3331: Steel Products Engineering Company, Division of Kelsey-Hayes Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1192, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Code no.3332: Massey-Ferguson, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 174,1505,1446, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Code no.3333: Comet Tool and Die Company and International Association of Machinists, District 9, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Code no.3334: Evinrude Motors and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Code no.3338: National Cash Register Company and NCR Employees' Independent Union, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Code no.3339: Goulds Pumps, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 3298, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Code no.3340: E.W. Bliss Co. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 4396, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Code no.3342: Diamond Chain Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1697, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Code no.3344: Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 645 of District 157; International Molders and Allied Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 250, 1966-1972 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Code no.3345: California Metal Trades Association, Printing Manufacturing and Service Division and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 68, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Code no.3347: Iowa Manufacturing Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Harmony Lodge 831 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Code no.7: Convair Division of General Dynamics and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Lodge 50, 1969- 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8: Hughes Aircraft Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Old Pueblo Lodge 933, 1961- 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Code no.9: Lockheed Missiles and Space Company and The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 508, 1968- 1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Code no.10: Martin Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 738,766,788, 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Code no.11: Martin Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 738, 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Code no.12: Martin Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 788, 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)